rakeback.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy policy of Rakeback.com

At [Rakeback.com](http://www.rakeback.com/ "Rakeback Site") we respect your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers the Rakeback.com’s use of personal information that the Rakeback.com collects when you use Rakeback.com. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

## Information Collection

Providing Information to Us. We collect Personal Information from you when you provide it to us. For example, if you register to our loyalty (rakeback) program, we collect Your name, email, username and poker room related information.

Communications With Us. If you communicate with us regarding the Web Site or the Rakeback.com Services, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication.

Analytic and Reporting Technologies. Like the operators of most web sites, we use analytic and reporting technologies to record Non-Personal Information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software and operating system types, clickstream patterns, and the dates and times that the Web Site and the Rakeback.com Services are accessed.

## Information Use

Rakeback.com uses the information it collects from you in a variety of ways, including using the information to customize features and advertising that appear on the Rakeback.com website. We also may provide your information to third parties, such as service providers, contractors, and advertisers, for a variety of purposes. For example, we may provide our advertisers with information about you and other visitors that will enable our advertisers to better target ads to specific types of visitors.

Rakeback.com reserves the right to use and to disclose to third parties all of the information that Rakeback.com collects online about you and other visitors in any way and for any purpose, with one important exception. Rakeback.com will not use the information that it collects online from you while you are using the Service, nor will Rakeback.com authorize third parties to use such information, to mail or email promotional offers directly to you unless you have specifically informed Rakeback.com that you would like to receive promotional offers from Rakeback.com and/or from third parties. If you choose to receive these promotional offers, then your information may be used for direct mail or email marketing.

Rakeback.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We respond to court orders or legal process to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Rakeback.com under confidentiality agreements. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Rakeback.com’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

## Cookies

Rakeback.com may set and access Rakeback.com cookies on your computer. A HTTP cookie is a small piece of data sent from our website and stored in your web browser while you are browsing our website. Read more about [cookies in Wikipedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie). If you wish to opt-out of cookies/tracking, please set cookies off in your Internet browser.

## Confidentiality and Security

Only Rakeback.com employees who need your personal information in their tasks have access to this information.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

If we change our Privacy Statement, we will post those changes on this page so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Users should check this policy frequently to keep abreast of any changes.
